hi everyone back on February 20th I
announced that I was going to go to 12
different cities in North America and
talk about my new book 12 rules for life
and a variety of other things and so we
arranged theaters and put those tickets
up for sale and they've proved very
popular I did the first one this week on
Sunday in New York at the Beacon Theater
to an audience of about 3,000 people and
it seemed to go very well the
consequence of that is that I'm now
announcing another 20 cities and this is
the video to make that announcement
I'm also appearing as a guest with
several other speakers including Matt
Dillahunty sam Harris a number of times
and also sam Harris and Douglas Murray
and so the announcements for those will
be included in the description of this
video as well all these talks are going
to occur from May through June and I'll
just list the cities you can get the
cities and the dates below Toronto
Washington Chicago Detroit Denver San
Francisco Seattle London Toronto Boston
Philadelphia and Houston Dallas Austin
and Phoenix Rick javac Washington and
Richmond Charlotte Nashville and Atlanta
Louisville Indianapolis and Milwaukee
Minneapolis Seattle and Vancouver that's
twice with Sam Harris Portland
Sacramento and San Diego Long Beach
Thousand Oaks and finally Dublin with
Sam Harris and Douglas Murray I've done
about 10 of these talks already three in
London one in Amsterdam one in LA San
Francisco Vancouver Toronto and New York
I've really looked forward to them and
it's a real privilege to be able to
speak about important issues pertaining
to psychological development with an
enthusiastic and involved crowd and I
hope that the lectures are useful and
and that there is useful for the people
that I'm speaking with as they are
engaging and worthwhile for me so if
you'd like to buy a ticket then I'd like
to see you there and I look forward to
seeing you in your hometown in May and
June so thanks very much for your
continued support I hope we get a chance
to have a meaningful and productive
evening in the very near future bye bye